paythru.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy - Paythru

Paythru adheres to the [GSMA privacy principles](http://www.gsma.com/publicpolicy/wp-content/uploads/2012/03/gsmaprivacyprinciples2012.pdf)

This policy applies to Paythru.com ("Site").

Paythru Ltd. ("Paythru" "us" or "we") respects the privacy of visitors to its website and its clients. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information and Anonymous Information you submit to us through our Site. "Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, email address or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.

By submitting Personal Information through the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy. Your Personal Information may be processed by us in the country where it was collected, as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

### Notification of changes

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our Services change and expand. If we make substantial changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated policy on this page and we will post notice that this Privacy Policy has changed in the client portal and in this policy. Unless otherwise provided, the revised terms will take effect when they are posted. Once any changes that we make to this Privacy Policy become effective, your continued use of the Site after such time will signify your acceptance of the new terms.

### This Site Contains Links to Other Sites

We are not responsible for 3rd party sites (sites other than those located at Paythru.com and Paythru.mobi) - and you understand we do not control the content or actions of 3rd party sites.

### Information we collect

We automatically collect browser and geographical information to maintain a record of User's or Visitor's activity on the Site. We use cookies to track Visitor and User trends and patterns and to allow you to login to the client portal. No user-identifiable information is stored in cookies or the browser/geographical information collected.

Users and Visitors always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. If you disable cookies on your browser, please note that some parts of our Site may not function as effectively, and you will not be able to access the client portal, as this requires cookies to be enabled. As an automatic process, our Web server software records a log file of IP addresses that access the Site.

We also collect IP address information but do not ordinarily link IP addresses to Users' Personal Information. However, we can and will use IP addresses to identify a User when we, in our sole discretion, determine that it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms and Conditions of Use or to protect our site, customers or others.

### The online client portal

The online client portal allows clients to manage their accounts, including billing, projects and their personal information. We may use your information for internal marketing purposes unless you have asked us not to. We will always give you the opportunity to stop receiving material from us within any marketing materials we send.

### Legal requests

Paythru cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud, theft, harassment and other rights. We can (and you authorise us to) disclose any information about you if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; (b) protect or defend the rights or property of Paythru or third parties; or (c) assist in an investigation.

### Security

We take security seriously, and employ several security measures in the handling and storage of your information. This includes SSL encryption in the client area and in other sensitive areas of our website. Please note however that with current technology, we cannot guarantee the security of your data as it travels over the Internet.

### Cookies

Please visit our Cookie policy for more information.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact us.
